A Guide to the Records of the University Club, 1925-2000
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
- Series XVIII: Residence and Use, 1957-1998
  - University Club Residents, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - House Rules and Regulations, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Vandalism, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Series XIX: Social Events, 1981-2000
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control, 1981-1988 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control - Financial and Statistical Information, 1986-1994 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Alcohol Use Policy and License, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Auction, 1993-1998 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Calvera and Hoge Art Show (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Cotillion, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Cotillion, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Invoices - Club Rentals I, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Invoices - Club Rentals II, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Invoices - Club Rentals I, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Invoices - Club Rentals II, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Invoices - Club Rentals III, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Karen Cecil Articles (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - The Long Way Home, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Member Opinion Poll Results (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - New River Cruise Company, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Newsletter, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Newsletters, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Newsletter, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Newsletter, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Newsletter, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Newsletter, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Newsletter, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Newsletter, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Newsletter, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Newsletter, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Newsletter, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Photographs - Kathy Hudson-Wiley Stained Glass (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Social Committee Correspondence, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Social Events, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Social Events, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Social Events, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Social Events, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Social Events, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Social Events, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Social Events, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Social Events, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Social Events, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Social Events, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Social Events, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Social Events, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Social Events, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Social Events, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Social Events, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Social Events, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Use and Rental of the University Club, 1988-1991 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Virginia Dare Cruise (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Virginia Tech Foundation Giving Report, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Visiting Artists - Gail Godwin, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Visiting Artists - Carol Hoge, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Visiting Artists - Senator William B. Hopkins, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Visiting Artists - Charlie Byrd, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Visiting Artists - Nikki Giovanni, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Visiting Artists - Ronlin Foreman, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Visiting Artists - Victoria Bond, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Visiting Artists - Andrea Anderson, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Visiting Artists - Trittico, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Visiting Artists - The Breskes, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Visiting Artists - Stephanie Nakasian and Hod O' Brien, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Visiting Artists - U.S. Navy Band, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - Visiting Artists - Chris Barry, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Visiting Artists - Ken Mulzet, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - Visiting Artists - Craig Fields, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - Visiting Artists - Gerry Timlin, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - Visiting Artists - Gerry Timlin, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - Visiting Artists - David Wiley, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - Visiting Artists - Gerry Timlin and Sharon Scully, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - Visiting Artists - Jeanne Schumann, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 74)
  - Visiting Artists - Gerry Timlin, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - Visiting Artists - Virginia Spence Carr (Box 6, Folder 76)
  - Visiting Artists - Wolf Von Eckardt (Box 6, Folder 77)
  - Fashion Show (Box 4, Folder 78)
- Series XX: Steinway Piano, 1989-1991
  - Steinway Piano, 1989-1991 (Box 6, Folder 79)
  - Steinway Brochure (Folder 1)